You're smart.
But what have you done?
You always say yes.
You just keep charging ahead.
Why did you say that?
Do you have to say it
aloud that I'm single?
I'll be your date.
Ouch!
After everything I found out from Sianong.
You thought I would be easy to kill?
You're caught now.
Dad, I want to protect her.
From her family's world.
You really think she knows nothing?
You think Chiara doesn't know
the kind of world her parents live in?
- Sir, are you okay? Medic, medic!
- She escaped.
- Medic!
- She escaped!
I don't believe you, Dad.
You're wrong about Chiara.
Mikoy, I know you love her.
Don't let yourself be blinded
by your feelings for her
just to believe she's innocent.
You saw Chiara yourself, Dad. Right?
Shopping, going out.
That's her only world.
That's why it's hard to believe
she's involved in her father's business.
Dear,
those kinds of syndicates,
they're family.
Loyalty runs deep,
that's why they're hard to take down.
That's why I believe
Chiara knows something
and I wouldn't be surprised if one day,
she ends up inheriting
the syndicate her family runs.
Check over there.
Chiara is different, Dad.
She's not like them.
Dad, you just don't know
her well enough yet.
That's why you think that way.
Also, she could never do whatever horrible
things her father is capable of
and she would never want
to enter the dirty world of her family.
My son,
no matter how kind she was to us, to you,
that doesn't mean she's
incapable of becoming one of them.
It doesn't mean she's not a Moraviano.
But Dad, I know her.
Chiara is a good person, Dad.
She's not like that.
Also Dad,
how did you even find out all of this?
Also, why do you have so many guns?
Dad, what are you going to do?
Mikoy, I…
I have a past.
Law enforcement, but I'm not the police.
Are you a gangster too?
I'm not a gangster.
Intelligence asset.
And that's when I started suspecting
especially after you got shot.
I thought you were handling land deals.
That was just my cover story.
You're really something, Dad.
So I could investigate this.
So what happened was,
I tracked down one of my friends
and he gave me information
about Viktor and the others.
That's enough.
It's not life-threatening.
Sir.
- What?
- Sir.
We've swept the entire area.
The house is clear,
there are no more explosives.
We cornered her.
But, she had a plan B.
She's not easy to corner.
We'll catch her eventually, sir.
We'll corner her again.
Looks like she got hit,
there's blood on her clothes, sir.
- Yes, sir.
- Maybe we can identify her
or maybe we already have
her record in the database.
‪ALEXANDRIA CORTEZ
‪AGENT
Alex…
And why should I trust you?
I don't need your trust.
Carlota called.
Bok.
There you go again.
Don't trust her, okay?
You already know that.
That's what you've said
before about Mikoy.
We're already here
and we've come this far because of that.
This isn't Henry.
Oh, please
I know you've sent him to kill me
because I've already become a loose end.
Why do you look like that?
Eat first.
Didn't anyone realize that?
I don't care, sir.
How's your wound?
It's okay.
It's a bit deep though.
It might take a while to heal.
Have you killed him?
No.
You're good.
I know you can do it alone
but you'd be even more formidable if,
you had someone with you.
A partner in crime.
Literally.
You know, while you're still recovering,
you can stay here.
Daddy, I smell porridge!
Wow, barbie!
Tali, my dear,
why don't you go to your room first?
Hi, barbie!
I'm Tali by the way.
May I have some porridge too?
Of course come here.
Tali, my dear
how about this.
You will go to your room
then Daddy will bring you some porridge.
Please?
Does it hurt?
Just a little.
Sis, she looks like you.
Come on, let's play.
Let's change her clothes
then let's make her a wound too.
Because of the new
information Mikoy obtained.
This could be very critical
to the case we're building
against the Moraviano.
That's valid.
I know where you're coming from,
and I can feel your concern.
Because of that new information.
But we still haven't caught her, sir.
Well, the point is,
all those years of frustration because
you never had a breakthrough in this case.
Now, we're slowly exposing them.
And because of your sacrifices,
we're close to succeeding
and finally getting justice
against the Valtrovis.
We got La Fornarina injured.
Once we catch her, It will be big.
Although I may not agree with it,
but what you did in Prague
was very creative,
and that was what put us here.
I also took some risks against
the Moravianos, just like you.
The day I failed to report to the office,
the truth is I was attacked too.
By one of Moraviano's men.
It's Carlota.
So you're telling me now
you could've been killed!
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew you'd get mad.
And, apparently,
I just inherited that from you, sir.
I decided to let her go.
Are you out of your goddamned mind?
I let her go because I know
Viktor will not be happy.
So I let her go to prove to her
that Viktor will move against her.
And once that happens,
she will turn against him.
And it's very possible
that I can turn her against Viktor.
That for you to turn her,
that Carlota must survive.
And she's ready to testify
against the Moravianos.
You know, I wanted to get mad
at you at first.
Thank you very much.
Looks like the story is finally
starting to go our way.
And in just a few more days, sir,
we'll finally bring down the Moravianos.
Guys the PA POP P is
already doing a sound check!
You know, if they just smile at me,
It's already enough for this year!
I'm ready to celebrate
Christmas and New Year.
Who's bias among all of them?
Bias? What is bias?
You know what? Seems like
you don't have Internet, Angelito.
Bias refers to your favorite in a group.
Oh, just like who's my favorite
in Avengers, right?
Just like that.
Actually, I just started
listening to their music.
Even here, there's still an assignment.
I also put an effort here, okay?
Even though I'm not into boy bands.
- You're really sweet!
- So sweet…
- You know what? Let's take a selfie.
- Sofie, wait.
Guys… I think you should just go first.
Huh?
Are you okay?
Why? You don't feel well?
Do you want me to come with you?
No need. I'm okay.
I just need to attend to something urgent
like, right now.
I mean, we can't go
anyway if you're not around.
No worries, just go have some fun!
This is our semestral entrance, right?
All right.
- Sofie.
I'm okay!
I'll wait to hear your stories, okay?
Wait, guys.
Do you really think she knows nothing?
That Chiara doesn't know about the world
her mother and father are involved in?
Mikoy, I know you love her.
Don't let yourself be blinded
by your feelings for her
just to believe she's innocent.
That's why I believe
Chiara knows something
and I wouldn't be surprised if one day
she ends up inheriting
the syndicate her family runs.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Tali can be a bit stubborn.
Actually…
her presence is comforting.
I'm curious.
You consciously chose to raise a child,
in such a chaotic world?
It wasn't hard for me.
Because I fell in love.
I was filled with so much love.
You know that feeling
where you feel like you can do anything?
That's how Tanya and I…
Tali's mother.
Isn't that what they say?
Love conquers all.
It's just that Tanya died
while giving birth to Tali.
But you know, the doctor did warn us
that her pregnancy was risky.
But we were determined
to build a family together.
So even if I'm alone now,
she will be protected,
she will always feel complete with love.
Oh, gosh.
I'll have something like that too.
Hey, hey, hey! Wait, wait, wait!
Angelito!
Angelito, are you okay?
Why are you following! Look what happened!
- You know each other?!
Wow, small world!
Out of all the cops,
it turns out you know Agent Kian.
By the way, Sir Kian,
you still remember me?
I'm Angelito, the one you helped before.
Of course. Unfortunately,
we don't have time to catch up today.
We're in a hurry.
He's right, we'll go ahead.
Hold on.
Is this about Mikoy?
Is there something I should worry about?
I can't give any information, Angelito.
Sofie, let's go.
Uh, Angelito,
I'll tell it to you next time.
It's a long story.
And this is not the right place and time.
So I'll go ahead, okay? Bye!
Okay, take care!
Why did you tell him?
He called.
Of course I couldn't resist,
I'm a father too.
I'd also want to know if my child is okay.
Thank God.
Are you sure? Because we heard
that you got injured.
You don't need to worry.
Dear…
I'm really okay.
That's why I got caught off guard.
What about that?
Mikoy can't see you while you're injured.
That's okay, I already got it covered
because Mikoy thinks I'm in Prague
so that should give him a few days
and buy me some time to heal up.
When it rains, it pours.
The setbacks just keep coming.
Is there something I should know?
Your chihuahua really can't be trusted.
And I'm sorry, my dear.
What's important is that you find
the agent she's talking to
and that's how you'll find out
where Carlota is.
So…
don't think about this anymore.
Just get some rest, okay?
And heal up, my dear.
Wow, what a fail!
Looks like we don't have
a match for Carlota here.
Just one look.
And I can tell we shouldn't
underestimate that enemy.
CURRENT ROLE:
SENIOR SPECIAL AGENT G.A.G.O.
I know a lot.
We can start from how Viktor got
the throne from Moraviano syndicate.
Aren't you curious what Viktor
offered La Morte Bianca
in exchange for all
that protection and power?
Sianong?
I'm working as an asset
for the government.
And I'm helping them build a case
against the Moravianos.
The syndicate suspected
of being run by the Valtrovis.
Mikoy, listen to me carefully.
You need to stay away from Chiara.
You're life is in danger.
Wait, what are you talking about?